

edwinfcau@gmail.com Portfolio Link











Figma











ceros



Illustrator After Effects ceros I'm a digital designer driven by innovation and engagement, specializing in web, apps, and social media platforms. I view design as a journey that collaborates with content to enhance experiences through critical design thinking and research — whether in UX/UI or digital visuals. I possess the expertise to skillfully employ prompt engineering and AI tools to elevate designs.

I excel in customizing designs and content to fit various devices, spanning from smartphones and tablets to larger monitors. What distinguishes my work is the unique blend of passion and skill I bring across layouts, graphics, product mapping, wireframing, typography, and colour palettes.

EDUCATION

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017 **General Assembly** (formerly Bitmaker)

Web Development Program

> Web Development Immersive progam

Jan 2001 - Aug 2001 Birmingham City University

UK exchange design course

> UK exchange program selected by Toronto Metropolitan University to partake in Birmingham

1998 1999 2000 2001 2002

Aug 2000 **UAL: Central Saint Martins**

Experimentational Design Course

> Experimentational design course using unconventional materials and concepts

Sep 1998 - Apr 2002 Toronto Metropolitan University (formerly Ryerson University)

2017

B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

> Fashion Design, Fashion Marketing, Consumer Product Design, some Graphic Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

earlier experiences listed on LinkedIn



Senior Designer, Digital & Multimedia • Borden Ladner Gervais LLP • Jan 2020 - Feb 2024

- > Creation of concepts and visuals to completion of digital products for <u>BLG</u> and subsidiary legal services BLG Beyond; from designing webpages and company apps to social media platform visuals. Balancing quality, speed, accuracy and consistency in delivering brand standards and goals
- > Acted as BLG Affinity group committee member (2021 2023)



Digital Designer • Blake, Cassels & Graydon LLP • Aug 2017 - Jan 2020

> Creation to completion of concepts, visuals and digital assets for the launch of <u>blakes.com</u>, webpages, client-facing marketing materials, internal communications, social media platform visuals, and print materials



Design Manager, Consumer Products • Thinkway Toys • Apr 2016 - Mar 2017

> Design Manager in licensed consumer products including Lucas Films Ltd. (Star Wars Rogue One), ©Disney/ Pixar (Cars 3), and Universal Studios (Despicable Me 3)



Associate, Online Product Approval • Disney Consumer Products (Disney Canada) • Nov 2013 - Mar 2016

- > Creative associate as part of Disney Canada OPA team on consumer softlines and hardlines products and packaging sold across Canada; including stores such as Walmart Canada and Canadian Tire
- > Working as a team in guiding 50+ licensees on 500+ products seasonally including ©Disney/Pixar and Frozen. Managing online product design approval process and meeting with vendors & licensees on communicating design goals and brand guides, to defining brand initiatives

DOLCE & GABBANA

Associate • Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy) • Feb 2013 - Sept 2013

> Brought 10 years of Canadian design experience abroad and resulted in an opportunity for Dolce & Gabbana in Milan; preparation and assistance on Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 RTW collections; and creation of look books